in the morning. This is early.
凌晨4点37分。 现在还早。
This is early even for me.
即使对我来说，现在也还早。
But But I got a flight this morning, so
但是，我今天早上有飞机，所以
got to get it in when you can get it in.
得抓紧时间把它弄进去。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
&gt;&gt; No one's out [music] here 4:30 in the
凌晨4点30分，这里没人。[音乐]
Whole city is yours.
整座城市都归你了。
I still haven't seen one person. Not one
我到现在还没见到一个人。 一个也没有
person.
。
Early one today cuz I have a flight this
今天一大早就得出发了，因为我早上有飞机
morning, so I have to
，所以
I got to drive to the airport now.
我现在得开车去机场了。
My windows don't roll down, so
我的车窗摇不下来，所以
I got to
我
open the car door every time I need to
每次想把手
reach outside.
伸到车外都得打开车门。
Nothing.
没有什么。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Made it.
成功了。
Uh
呃，
I'm here to surf, and David, the kid who
我是来冲浪的，给
checked me in, said that there are
我办理入住的那个叫大卫的小伙子说这里有
humongous waves, so
巨大的海浪，
Wow.
哇！
How are the waves?
海浪情况如何？
&gt;&gt; The waves? Right now, they're huge.
海浪？ 现在它们体型巨大。
&gt;&gt; Are you going to come surfing with us?
你要和我们一起去冲浪吗？
&gt;&gt; No, I don't surf actually.
不，我其实不冲浪。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
&gt;&gt; I haven't done it yet.
我还没做过呢。
&gt;&gt; Nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你。
&gt;&gt; Hey, nice to meet you, my man. Whatever
嘿，很高兴见到你，兄弟。
you need, just come by to the lobby.
您需要什么，就到大厅来一趟。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hello from El Salvador. So, I'm here on
来自萨尔瓦多的问候。 所以，我这次来是进行
a very short and somewhat last minute
一次非常短暂且有点临时起意的
surf trip. Friend of mine called was
冲浪之旅。 我的一个朋友打电话
like, "Hey, you want to go on a quick
来说：“嘿，你想去
surf trip to El Salvador?" And I was
萨尔瓦多来一次短途冲浪之旅吗？” 我当时
like,
就想：
"I'm in."
“我参加。”
Look at this barbed wire. It's like
看看这铁丝网。 它就像
regular barbed wire, razor wire, and
普通的铁丝网、刀片刺网，
then they put glass in the concrete. So,
然后他们还在混凝土里加入了玻璃。 所以，
if you were to try to grab it, it would
如果你试图抓住它，它会……
This is really effective barbed wire.
这真是非常有效的带刺铁丝网。
Hola.
你好。
That is all the Spanish I speak.
这就是我全部的西班牙语水平。
When I say it's a short trip, so
我说这是一次短途旅行，所以
I made this diagram. Yesterday, we
我画了这个示意图。 昨天我们
arrived and went surfing. Today, we go
到了之后就去冲浪了。 今天，我们去
surfing. Tomorrow, we go surfing and we
冲浪。 明天我们去冲浪，​​然后就
leave. Very, very, very short trip.
离开。 非常非常非常短的行程。
There is one minor issue, which is
有一个小问题，那就是
tomorrow, on the day that we surf and
明天，也就是我们冲浪然后
then leave, tomorrow is Mother's Day.
离开的那天，是母亲节。
We're all married on this trip.
这次旅行我们都像是结婚了一样。
We all have kids on this trip.
我们这次旅行都带着孩子。
wives on Mother's Day. But, I think it's
母亲节那天，我们谁都陪不了老婆。 但是，我认为
important to stay positive.
保持积极的心态很重要。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Oh my god.
我的天哪。   这
&gt;&gt; What's up?
是怎么回事？
&gt;&gt; Dude, I've been a huge fan since I was a
老兄，我从小就是你的铁杆粉丝
little kid.
。
&gt;&gt; And what, you guys all came down here to
你们都来这里
surf?
冲浪吗？   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah, very much so.
，确实如此。
&gt;&gt; And how do you like it here?
你觉得这里怎么样？
&gt;&gt; Dude, it's beautiful. El Salvador is an
老兄，真漂亮。 萨尔瓦多是一个
awesome country.
很棒的国家。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; So, this little walk that I'm on right
所以，我现在正在进行的这段小小的散步
now, this is like the most exploring of
，就像是
Salvador I'll have the opportunity to
我能有机会对萨尔瓦多
do. And this area is like this is like a
进行的最深入的探索。 这片区域就像一个
real touristy surfing beach area.
典型的旅游冲浪海滩区。
But, I will say even though I have just
但是，虽然我只
like a little exposure, I know this
接触过一点点，但我知道这并
isn't indicative of the whole country.
不能代表整个国家的情况。
Everyone here has been great. Also, they
这里每个人都很棒。 此外，他们
love Bitcoin here.
这里也很喜欢比特币。   一幅画
Painting of a beautiful woman holding a
描绘了一位美丽的女子手捧
pearl and the pearl is
珍珠，而这颗珍珠象征着
Bitcoin. Bitcoin accepted here. Bitcoin
比特币。 这里接受比特币。 比特币
surf board. Bitcoin garbage can. Another
冲浪板。 比特币垃圾桶。 又一个
Bitcoin garbage can. I believe this
比特币垃圾桶。 我认为这位
graffiti artist's name is Bitcoin.
涂鸦艺术家的名字是比特币。
Bitcoin accepted here. Aceptamos todas
这里接受比特币。 接受所有
las formas de pago. Pajo.
形式的帕戈。 帕霍。
Cash money's
现金就是
Bitcoin. True story, this uh beach
比特币。 说真的，
behind me, it's called Bitcoin Beach.
我身后的这片海滩，叫做比特币海滩。
See?
看？
We are in Bitcoin Beach.
我们身处比特币海滩。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; This is our hotel. It's great, very
这就是我们的酒店。 很棒，非常
nice, but this is my favorite part.
好，但这是我最喜欢的部分。
Ready? So, the guy that owns this hotel
准备好？ 所以，这家酒店的老板
owns the hotel to the They're small
拥有这家酒店。它们都是小型
hotels. Owns the hotel on that side and
酒店。 拥有那边的酒店和
the hotel on that side. To connect all
那边的酒店。 为了连接这
three hotels
三家酒店，
he built this little walkway here.
他在这里修建了这条小走廊。   沿着
And like go down the walkway this way
这条小路往下走​​，
and it takes you to that hotel. Go up
就能到那家酒店了。 沿着
the walkway this way and takes you to
这条小路走上去，就能到那家
that hotel.
酒店了。
And you're right on the
你说得对，这
How cool is that?
太酷了！
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; The surfing we've been doing has been
我们最近的冲浪体验
rad. So, we linked up with these local
太棒了。 所以，我们和当地这些
guys here. Um one of whom, Brian, was in
人联系上了。 其中一位名叫布莱恩，曾参加过
the Olympics for surfing.
奥运会冲浪比赛。
His main job is to make sure we don't
他的主要工作是确保我们不会
drown, but he also teaches us how to
溺水，但他也会教我们
surf a little.
一些冲浪技巧。
What's the What's the surf report today?
今天的冲浪报告是什么？
&gt;&gt; Pretty good. 5 6 ft, maybe 6. But, uh
不错。  5英尺6英寸，也许6英尺。但是，呃，
firing good way, good condition,
射击效果很好，状态良好，
glassing in the morning.
早上用玻璃进行测试。
No people around secret spot.
秘密地点周围没有人。
&gt;&gt; And you're going to you're going to make
你会
sure we don't drown.
确保我们不会被淹死。   对
&gt;&gt; Yeah, exactly.
，没错。
&gt;&gt; And then we pile into their pickup truck
然后我们
with like a hundred surf boards and they
和大约一百块冲浪板挤进他们的皮卡车，他们
take us to the the surf spot.
把我们送到冲浪地点。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[music]
然后我们就去冲浪，感觉棒极了。
&gt;&gt; And though I'm not at all a good surfer,
虽然我冲浪技术很差，但
I do like surfing. Check out this
我确实喜欢冲浪。 看看这张
picture. This is me today.
照片。 这就是现在的我。
Not bad.
不错。
It's not that I'm a bad surfer, it's
不是说我冲浪技术不好，而是
I'm not a good surfer.
我冲浪技术不够好。
You know what I mean?
你知道我的意思？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; It is [music] 5:31 in the morning. We're
现在是[音乐] 早上5点31分。 我们
leaving today. Today's Sunday, but
今天就要离开。 今天是星期天，
today's also Mother's Day and um to
也是母亲节。为了
alleviate the guilt of not being with my
减轻
wife or my children on Mother's Day, I I
母亲节当天不能陪伴妻子和孩子的内疚感，我
planned a special thing for them this
今天早上为他们安排了一件特别的事情
morning. This is the MacGuffin. This is
。 这就是关键道具。 这是
when I leave. We're going to put this in
我离开时她将会看到的假礼物。 我们要把它放进
refrigerator. This is fancy cookies.
冰箱里。 这是精致的饼干。
This big one,
这个大的，
this is the secret present.
这是秘密礼物。
This I'm going to have like I'm going to
我要把这个
hide it and then she's going to get it
藏起来，然后
on
在
Mother's Day morning. And when you open
母亲节早上给她。 当你打开
it, see don't open with a knife, a
它的时候（注意不要用刀打开），会
balloon comes out that says Happy
弹出一个写着“
Mother's Day and then there's like a
母亲节快乐”的气球，然后
bunch of presents and stuff in there and
里面还有一堆礼物和东西，以及
presents for the kids.
给孩子们的礼物。
So, it's not like I didn't do anything.
所以，并不是我什么都没做。   没
It's fine, right?
问题吧？
&gt;&gt; This is your get out of jail free card.
这是你的免罪金牌。
&gt;&gt; No, it's because I love her and I love
不，那是因为我爱她，也爱
my family, man.
我的家人。
&gt;&gt; Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; And I left that package so it'd be
我把包裹放在
apartment door first thing this morning.
公寓门口，这样今天早上就能第一时间送到我们公寓门口了。
I know I'm on an indulgence surf trip
我知道我
with the boys when I should be there,
应该待在家里，但我却和哥们儿们一起享受冲浪之旅，
but it does show a lot of effort.
但这确实表明我付出了很多努力。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hello, Daddy.
你好，爸爸。
&gt;&gt; Did Franny, did Mommy like her surprise
弗兰妮，妈妈喜欢她的惊喜
box?
盒子吗？   是的
&gt;&gt; Yes, she loved it.
，她很喜欢。   好的
&gt;&gt; Okay, good. It was a nice big surprise?
。 真是个惊喜！   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; Okay, she's not mad at me for going
好吧，她没有因为我
surfing on Mother's Day?
母亲节去冲浪而生我的气？
&gt;&gt; No.
不。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]